(Sheldon:)...but I think we may be looking
at my new Tuesday hamburger.
(Leonard:)Your old Tuesday hamburger
will be so brokenhearted.
(Sheldon:)Way ahead of you.
(Sheldon:)I was thinking of moving Big Boy to
Thursdays and just dropping Souplantation.
- Really?
- Yeah.
(Sheldon:)The name always confused me, anyway.
Souplantation.
(Sheldon:)You can't grow soup.
- So how's everything?
- Terrific.
You'll be happy to know I plan to come
every Tuesday for the foreseeable future.
Really? Oh, yay. Heh.
(Sheldon:)Who do I speak to about
permanently reserving this table?
(Penny:)I don't know, a psychiatrist?
PENNY:
So, hey.
- How are things with you and Leslie?
- Oh.
(Leonard:)To be honest,
I don't think it's going to work out.
(Penny:)Oh, that's too bad.
Well, hey, don't worry.
I'm sure there's someone out there
who's just right for you.
(Leonard:)Well, what did she mean by that?
(Leonard:)Was that just a generic platitude
or was that a subtle bid for attention?
(Sheldon:)You know why this hamburger
surpasses the Big Boy?
This is a single-decker,
whereas the Big Boy is a double-decker.
(Sheldon:)This has a much more satisfying
meat-to-bun-to-condiment ratio.
- Are you even listening to me?
- Of course I'm listening.
(Sheldon:)Blah, blah, hopeless Penny delusion,
blah, blah, blah.
(Leonard:)Okay, then.
(Leonard:)You know, you can grow
the ingredients for soup.